export const questionsList = [{
    question: 'Who is the leading scorer in NBA History?',
    answer: 'LeBron James'
},
{
    question: 'Who has the most 3 pointers in NBA History?',
    answer: 'Stephen Curry'
},
{
    question: 'Which football quarterback has 7 championships and widely regarded as the greatest quarterback of all time?',
    answer: 'Tom Brady'
},
{
    question: 'Which quarterback did Tom Brady lose to twice in the superbowl?',
    answer: 'Eli Manning'
},
{
    question: 'Who won the 2024 NBA Championship?',
    answer: 'Boston Celtics'
},
{
    question: 'Which MLB player was a superstar for the Yankees for one year and decided to go to the Mets in the 2024 offseason?',
    answer: 'Juan Soto'
},
{
    question: 'Who won the world series in 2024?',
    answer: 'LA Dodgers'
},
{
    question: 'Who won the Superbowl in 2025?',
    answer: 'Eagles'
},
{
    question: 'What is the tennis tournament in New York City called that happens every year?',
    answer: 'US Open'
},
{
    question: 'Which past NBA Player has the most widely known shoe brand?',
    answer: 'Michael Jordan'
},
]